Guide to the Partners for Livable Communities records, 1960-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 3: Culture Builds Community, 1978-2012; (24 boxes)
  - Gem Charrette: Summary Report, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Gem Theater, Cultural & Performing Arts Center, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Going to Scale: Culture Builds Community Package, 2011 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation Resource Guide, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - HACE Best Practices, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - How to Incorporate Arts and Culture into Neighborhood Business District Revitalization Programs, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Howard Heinz Endowment Final Report, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Imagine a Great City, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Imagining Cultural Strategies for Houston's Older Adults and Immigrants, 2012 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Institutions as Fulcrums of Change, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Institutions as Fulcrums of Change: A Creative Reimagination of Every Community's Resources, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Integrating Applewood with Flint, Michigan, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Interim Reports and Specialized Surveys of the Social Impact of the Arts Projects, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Key Issues Relating to the Wild Kingdom in the City, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - La Comunidad: Design, Development, and Self-Determination in Hispanic Communities, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - La Comunidad: Making the Case for Arts, Culture, and Community Development in Latino Communities, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Lessons from the Shifting Sands Initiative, 2010 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Libraries are Good Businesses, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Living Above the Library, 2006 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Living Museums: Assets for Economic and Community Development, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan Performing Arts Collaboration Visioning Session, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Mobilizing Arts and Cultural Resources for Community Development, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Mobilizing Culture to Build Community, 2011 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Mt. Pleasant Temporium Final Report, 2011 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Museums in the Life of the City, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Museums in the Life of the City: Strategies for Community Partnerships, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Museums in the Social and Economic Life of a City, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Neighborhood Open Space Amenity Strategies, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Neighborhood Open Space Amenity Strategies, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Neighborhood Reinvestment and Training Institute in New Orleans: Mobilizing Arts and Cultural Resources for Community Building, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Neighborhood Reinvestment and Training Institute in New Orleans: Mobilizing Arts and Cultural Resources for Community Building, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Neighborhood Reinvestment Training Institute in New Orleans: Mobilizing Arts and Cultural Resources for Community Development, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Neighborhood Reinvestment Training Institute in Chicago: Developing An Arts-Based Economic Development Strategy in Your Community, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhood Reinvestment Training Institute in San Francisco,: Mobilizing Arts and Cultural Resources for Youth and Community Development., 2002 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Reinvestment Training Institute in Washington, DC: Mobilizing Arts and Cultural Resource for Community Building., 2004 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - New Vision for the Public Library Working Session Conference Materials, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - New Vision for the Public Library Working Session Conference Materials, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Notes from Culture Builds Community All-Grantee Open Space Meeting at the Abington Arts Center, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Opportunity for Dialogue Binder, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Parks and Recreation Departments Strategic Assessment, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Partners for Livable Communities Invests in Culture: Economic Justice & Opportunity, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Partners' Wellness Agenda, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Partnership Planning Workshop Text, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Phase II Report Public Markets as a Vehicle for Social Integration and Upward Mobility, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia Culture Builds Community Initiative, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Placemaking and Design through Arts & Culture, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Plan for Increasing Private Sector Support for Public Libraries in the State of California, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Plan for Increasing Private Sector Support for Public Libraries in the State of California, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Planning Grant by the Pew Trust Final Report, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Plymouth Christian Youth Center - Five Year Strategic Plan 2007 - 2012, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Preserving Everyone's History, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Prince George's County Gateway Arts District Planning Study, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Proceedings from the African American Heritage Tourism and Community Development Forum Kansas City, Missouri, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Profile of the Design Profession, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Public Library in Partnership with Community's Request for Participation, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Public Markets as a Vehicle for Social Integration and Upward Mobility, Phase One Report, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Public Markets: A Fulcrum of Change for the Community, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Renaissance: Museums as Bridges to Community Renewal, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Report on Capri Theatre Facilitated Forum Sessions, North Minneapolis, 2006 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Report on Cultural Learning Strategies, Neighborhood Works Multifamily Initiative/Neighborhood Reinvestment Corporation, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Report on Orlando Forum on New Cultural Policy, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Report to the Cultural Plan Study Committee; Charlotte, NC, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Requests and Resources: 1998-2000 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for Chattanooga Venture, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Riverside City and County Public Library: A Community Vision for the Central Library, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Shifting Sands Initiative Conference: Arts and Community - Excellence and Equity, 2007 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Shifting Sands, Arts Culture and Neighborhood Change, 2008 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Site Visit Report on the Bessie Smith Hall Project, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Social Capital and Community Development through Arts and Culture, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Social Impact of the Arts Project (SIAP) Report on the Culture Builds Community Grantee Focus Groups, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Stories for Change, 2012 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Strengthening Communities Through Cultural Strategies, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Strengthening the Economy through Arts & Culture, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Summary of Workshop Proceedings on "Establishing Planning Priorities/Community Demand for the Arts", 1981 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - The Arts and Culture in Wilmington, Delaware, 2012 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - The City and the Arts: A Civic Handbook of Grants Program, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - The Douglas Redd Fellowship Program: Workshop Curriculum for Fellows, 2011 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - The Douglas Redd Fellowship Program: Workshop Curriculum for Fellows, 2011 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - The Douglas Redd Fellowship Prospectus 2011-2012 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - The Role of the Museum, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - The Willing Community: A Journey Forward to the Place We Want, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Transcription of Johnson County Community College Retreat, 1998 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Using All Assets: Non Traditional Resources for Community Development, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Wild Kingdoms in the City: Conference Proceedings, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Workbook for the Rockefeller Foundation Retreat, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Series 4: New Civics, 1974-2012; (27 boxes)
  Series 4, New Civics, contains four subseries, Benchmarks and Indices, Leadership for Change, Regional Strategies, and Visioning and Local Participation that focus on developing successful leadership strategies to create community-centered programs through a cooperative effort between local government and private businesses.
  - Subseries 4.1: Benchmarks and Indices, 1974-2012; (7 boxes)
    - A Practical Guide to Creating Regional Change, 1997 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - American Fitness Index for Indianapolis, IN, 2008 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - American Institute of Architects Indicators for Grand Rapids, MI, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Bob McNulty's Principles of Livability, 2011 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Community Indicators - Volume One: PEOPLE, 1996 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Community Indicators - Volume Two: ECONOMY, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Community Indicators - Volume Three: ENVIRONMENT, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Community Reinvestment Scorecard for Chattanooga, NC, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Community Reinvestment Scorecard for Chattanooga, NC, con't, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Community Reinvestment Scorecard: Identifying Resources, Building Partnerships and Scoring Progress, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Community Reinvestment Scorecard: Identifying Resources, Building Partnerships and Scoring Progress, con't, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Community Reinvestment Scorecard: Identifying Resources, Building Partnerships and Scoring Progress, con't, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Creating Globally Competitive Communities, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Data Analysis Workbook: The First Steps in a Community Reinvestment System Self-Assessment, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Environmental Education Report: Urban Quality of Life, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Environmental Education Report: Urban Quality of Life, con't., 1981 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Final Benchmarking Report, Noblesville, Indiana, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Final Benchmarking Report, Noblesville, Indiana, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Grand Alliance: Toward a Definition of Livability for All, 2010-2011 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Human Investment Partnership: Achieving Benchmarks for Exceptional People, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - In Pursuit of Livability: A Strategic Planning Cooperative Background Paper on Benchmarks and Indices, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - In Pursuit of Livability: A Strategic Planning Cooperative, October 20-21, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - In Pursuit of Livability: A Strategic Planning Cooperative, October 20-21, 1995, con't (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Indicators for State of the Region, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Indicators for State of the Region, con't, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Lake Tahoe/Truckee Reinvestment Scorecard Workshop Notebook, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Lake Tahoe/Truckee Reinvestment Scorecard Workshop Presentation, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Livability Assesment Survey, The, 2009 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Livability Charrette in Frederick, Maryland, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Livability Charrette in Frederick, Maryland, con't, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Livability Charrette in Frederick, Maryland, con't, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Livability Charrette in Frederick, Maryland, con't, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Livability Index of American Communities Summary Report, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Local Government, Cultural Development, Evaluation, and Benchmarking, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Local Government, Cultural Development, Evaluation, and Benchmarking, cont, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Making Cities Livable from Environment Education Report, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - National Awards Program for America's Most Livable Communities, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - National Awards Program for America's Most Livable Communities Completed Notebook, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - National Livability Binder: Binder One, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - National Livability Binder: Binder Two, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - National Livability Report: Background Report Highlights, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - National Livability Report: Draft and Manuscript, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - National Livability Report: Research Findings, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Oregon Benchmarks: Setting Measurable Standards for Progress, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - The Potomac Index, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Report to San Bernardino County, California, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 4.2: Leadership for Change, 1974-2012; (7 boxes)
    - Beyond Confrontation: Development with Conservation, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - A Blueprint for Change: Diversity as a Civic Asset, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Breman Declaration - March 13-15, 1997: Business and Municipality/New Partnership for the 21st Century (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Bridge Builders Award Honoring Visionary Leaders in America, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Bridge Builders Award Honoring Visionary Leaders in America - Insert for Years 2001-2003 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Bridge Builders I Awards Program, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Bridge Builders II Awards Program, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Bridge Builders III Awards Program, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Bridge Builders IV Awards Program, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Bridge Builders VI Awards Program, 2002 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Bridge Builders VII Awards Program, 2003 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Bridge Builders VIII Awards Program, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Bridge Builders IX Awards Program, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Bridge Builders X Awards Program, 2008 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Building Partnerships: The President's Task Force on Private Sector Initiatives, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Business and the Municipalities: New Partnership for the 21st Century, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Business at the Table: The Employer Drive for Higher Education Attainment, 2012 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Business Leadership Groups Best Practices, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Business/Government Partnerships Boost Public Leisure Opportunities, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Chattanooga Venture, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Cities in Transition: Asian Pacific Islander Americans, An Asset to America's Future, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Cities in Transition: Hispanics in the United States, 1984 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Cities in Transition: The National Asian Pacific Islander American Project Profile Compendium, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Consultancy Report to the Manitoba Foundation's Council, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Conversations Across the Barricade, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Cooperating for Change: Steps to Strategic Action, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Corporate Community Involvement in Building Partnerships: The President's Task Force on Private Sector Initiatives, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Dayton Takes Action: A Retreat of the Downtown Dayton Partnership, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Dayton Takes Action: A Retreat of the Downtown Dayton Partnership, con't, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - "Die Stadt Als Unter Nehmer Mit Einer": German translation of The Entrepreneurial American Community, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Doing More with Less: Challenge of the 90's pamphet, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Enterprise in the Nonprofit Sector, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Green Plus Chamber & Community Awards 2011 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Harvest Foundation Board Retreat Notes, 2003 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Hispanic and Ibero-American Influences in U.S. Design - Draft Report on Quincentenary Organizations, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Hispanic Heritage in the Multicultural City, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - How to Get Started? Collaboration as a Way to Go, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Ideal and Trends, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - In Pursuit of Livability Binder, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - In Pursuit of Livability Binder, con't, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Indiana Cities Conference on Community Initiatives, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Indiana Cities Conference on Community Initiatives, con't, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Indiana Cities Conference on Community Initiatives, con't, 1994 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Indiana Cities Conference on Community Initiatives, con't, 1994 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Initiative to Strengthen Neighborhood Inner-Group Assets Grantee Meeting, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Initiative to Strengthen Neighborhood Inner-Group Assets Grantee Meeting, con't, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - International Lyon Symposium 1987, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Journeying Forward: a Bold Initiative, a Collaborative Partnership, a Strong Community, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Latin Roots in the Built Environment, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Leadership for Community Empowerment, 1994 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Livable Cities: How Small Grants Programs Can Make a Difference, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Livable Cities: How Small Grants Programs Can Make a Difference, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Livable Cities: How Small Grants Programs Can Make a Difference, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Local Official's Guide to Working with Clergy and Congregations, A, 2010 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Making Friends, Making a Difference: Concern for People, Communities and the Environment -- A Way of Life, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Making the Connections: Learning the Art of Stakeholder Engagement, a Resource Guide for the Annie Casey Foundation, 1991 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Mary Matthews Playground Report, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Media and Livability: Improving Relationships and Coverage, 1979 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Midsize City - Exploring its Unique Place in Urban Policy, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Models of Innovation: Community University Partnerships, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - National Advisory Body of the State of Arkansas, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - New Civics in Livability Digest, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - New Civics: Leadership from a Different Perspective, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - New Designs for Urban Improvement Through Public/Private Partnership, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Ossabaw Foundation, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Partners and Hispanic Issues, 1992 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Partners Council of 1984 Recognition Awards Contained Within an Issue of Livability Magazine (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Partners Council of 1984 Recognition Awards Contained Within an Issue of Livability Magazine (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Pollyanna, or Is The Glass Half Full?, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Public/Private Partnerships and Urban Revitalization in the U.S.: An Opportunity for Learning from America, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Public/Private Partnerships and Urban Revitalization in the U.S.: An Opportunity for Learning from America, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Report to Virginia Mountain Housing, Incorporated Staff Retreat, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse on Downtown Development Organizations, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Role of Nonprofit Organizations in Renewing Community - National Civic Review, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Role of Nonprofit Organizations in Renewing Community - National Civic Review, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Roles of Non-Government Groups in Urban Change: Study Tour Report and Recommendations, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Roles of Non-Government Groups in Urban Change: Study Tour Report and Recommendations, con't, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Safe Neighborhoods and Community Investment Act of 1993: Odyssey 2000 Final Report (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Selective Guide to Organizations and Institutions: Hispanic and Caribbean Influence on Design, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Selective Guide to Organizations and Institutions: Hispanic and Caribbean Influence on Design, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Selective Guide to Organizations and Institutions: Hispanic and Caribbean Influence on Design, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Shaping America: Hispanic Heritage in the US Environment, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Shaping America: Hispanic Heritage in the US Environment, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Spanish Legacies in the Built Environment-Final Report, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Summary Minutes of the Meeting of the Advisory Committee of the National Advisory Board of Cornerstones Community Partnership of Santa Fe, New Mexico, July 12, 1997 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Taking the Town-Gown Initiative, 2003 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Three Years of Partnership: Making Resources Count, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Town-Gown Dynamics: Best Practices, 1997 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Workbook for Team Leaders and Facilitators, 1997 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 4.3: Regional Strategies, 1974-2012; (5 boxes)
    - Alpine Diamond: Lyon, Geneva, Turin, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Arts and Service to the Region: Cultural Planning and the Triad, 1992 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Background Set of Materials for the Santa Fe Land Use Resource Center, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Boundless 21st Century City, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Bridge the Gap, Bridging the Divide: Making Regions Work Better for Everyone, Shaping the Federal Agenda - Binder, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Bridge the Gap, Bridging the Divide: Making Regions Work Better for Everyone, Shaping the Federal Agenda - Binder, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Bridging the Divide: Making Regions Work for Everyone Shaping the Federal Agenda Conference Summary, December 13-14, 1999., 2000 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Community Empowerment Manual; 2nd Edition, 2011 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Crossing the Line: The New Regional Dynamics., 2000 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Crossing the Line: National Leadership Forum on Regional Strategies Binder, pt 1., 1999 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Crossing the Line: National Leadership Forum on Regional Strategies Binder, pt 2., 1999 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Crossing the Line: National Leadership Forum on Regional Strategies Binder, pt 3., 1999 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Crossing the Line: National Leadership Forum on Regional Strategies proceeding and workbook, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Crossing the Line: National Leadership Forum on Regional Strategies Final Report, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Europe's Alpine Diamond Region, 1998 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Excerpts from A Temporary Paradise? A Look at the Special Landscape of the San Diego Region, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Finding Success with Smart Growth- Maryland, 1999 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Getting There: Transportation Choices for Our Region: Vision and Ideas booklet, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Getting There: Transportation Choices for Our Region: Vision and Ideas packets, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Getting There: Transportation Choices for Our Region: Vision and Ideas packets, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Here Today and Gone Tomorrow? The Need For Asset Management in Las Cruces, New Mexico, 1991 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Leadership Forum Program: Crossing the Line, 1999 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Livable Brisbane: A Plan for Australia's Most Livable City, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Materials from "Mayors and the Media: Steps Towards Regional Solutions" Forum, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - National Capital Region Leadership Retreat Summary Report, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Practical Guide to Creating Regional Change, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Proposal For Las Cruces, New Mexico, 1991 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Regionalism and Talk Turning to Action, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Regionalism and Talk Turning to Action, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Regionalism and Talk Turning to Action, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - The Regionalist: Initiatives for America's Regions (Summer 1997) (Box 103, Folder 1)